A Guide to the Budget Working Papers of the Director, Virginia Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2006-2020
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Budget Working Papers of the Director, Virginia Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2006-2020
The Library of Virginia
53827
47 cubic feet (47 Boxes)
Virginia Dept. of Planning and Budget
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 53827 was transferred 27 February 2023.
Historical Information
Established by an Act of Assembly in 1976, the Dept. of Planning and Budget was created through the merging of the Division of the Budget and the Division of State Planning and Community Affairs. The duties of the Dept. of Planning and Budget include: the development and direction of an integrated policy analysis, planning and budgeting process within State government; the development, storage, retrieval and dissemination of data on the social, economic, physical and governmental aspects of the State; the formulation of an executive budget; conduct policy and program analysis for the Governor; the establishment of planning districts and standard metropolitan statistical areas; and the development and operation of a system of standardized reports of program and financial performance for management.
Scope and Content
Budget Working Papers of the Director, Virginia Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2006-2020, are housed in 47 boxes and are arranged in original order. These budget files of Director Daniel S. Timberlake include budget forecasts, budget amendments, budget issue files, budget requests, budget tracks, documentation for budget meetings with the Governor, legislative files, plans, reduction strategies, reports, and other records related to budget development.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Budget Working Papers, 2006-2020 (Accession 53827)
Contents List
- Budget Working Papers, 2006-2020., Extent: 47 boxes. (Box 1-47)
  - Amendments - Executive, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Amendments - Governor, 2013. (Box 15)
  - Base Budget, 2008. (Box 25)
  - Base budget, 2012. (Box 13)
  - Budget action reports, 2007. (Box 28)
  - Budget amendments, 2012. (Box 13)
  - Budget Crossover, 2010. (Box 7)
  - Budget Crossover issues, 2011. (Box 5)
  - Budget Crossover Report, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Budget Crossover, 2016. (Box 30)
  - Budget Development - Fall, 20006. (Box 28)
  - Budget Development, 2008-2010. (Box 24)
  - Budget Development, 2008-2010. (Box 25)
  - Budget Development, 2010. (Box 9)
  - Budget Development Track, 2010. (Box 7)
  - Budget Development (2012-2014), 2012. (Box 17)
  - Budget - Executive, 2008. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Final, 2015 Dec. (Box 29)
  - Budget Forecasts, 2009. (Box 5)
  - Budget Forecasts, 2016. (Box 29)
  - Budget issues (2008 General Assembly), 2008. (Box 23)
  - Budget issues, 2008-2009. (Box 19)
  - Budget issues, 2009. (Box 20)
  - Budget issues - 2010 Summer, 2010. (Box 18)
  - Budget issues, 2012. (Box 17)
  - Budget issues - 2013 General Assembly, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Budget issues - 2017 General Assembly, 2017. (Box 29)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2006 Oct-Nov. (Box 27)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2006 Nov-Dec. (Box 27)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2007 Sept. (Box 26)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2007 Oct-Nov. (Box 26)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2007 Nov-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2008 Aug. (Box 26)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2008 Sept-Nov. (Box 21)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor - 2008 Reconvened Session, 2008. (Box 22)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2009 Sept-Dec. (Box 1)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2009 June-Sept. (Box 1)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2010 Jan-Feb. (Box 1)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2010 Mar-Apr. (Box 8)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2010 Aug-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Mar-Apr. (Box 4)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Aug-Sept. (Box 10)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Oct-Nov. (Box 10)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Nov. (Box 11)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Nov-Dec. (Box 11)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2011 Dec. (Box 11)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2012 May. (Box 14)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2012 Oct-Nov. (Box 15)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2012 Nov-Dec. (Box 13)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor - 2013 General Assembly, 2013. (Box 15)
  - Budget meetings with the Governor, 2015 Oct-Dec. (Box 30)
  - Budget planning, 2011. (Box 12)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 2009. (Box 7)
  - Budget Reduction Strategies, 2008. (Box 8)
  - Budget Reports - 2013 Session, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Budget requests, 2008. (Box 26)
  - Budget savings, 2010. (Box 6)
  - Budget Tracks, 2008. (Box 23)
  - Budget Tracks, 2008-2009. (Box 2)
  - Budget Tracks, 2008-2010. (Box 2)
  - Budget Tracks, 2011. (Box 5)
  - Budget Tracks, 2011. (Box 10)
  - Conference Report work papers, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Crossover -Budget concerns, 2008 General Assembly, 2008. (Box 22)
  - Education (K-12), 2008-2010. (Box 24)
  - Education issues, 2008-2010. (Box 19)
  - Federal budget facts, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Final Approved Reduction Plan for FY2010, 2010. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly budget materials, 2009. (Box 19)
  - General Assembly responses, 2009. (Box 18)
  - Governor's Budget Actions, 2011. (Box 8)
  - Governor's Budget Adjustments, 2010. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Reduction Plan, 2007. (Box 26)
  - Governor's Saving and Spending, 2010. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Veto Information, 2010. (Box 9)
  - Inventory of Agency Components, 2008-2010. (Box 25)
  - Legislation, 2007. (Box 26)
  - Legislative concerns (2008 General Assembly), 2008. (Box 23)
  - Non-General Fund Cash Review, 2009. (Box 5)
  - Operating requests, 2008. (Box 25)
  - Reductions - Budget, 2008. (Box 21)
  - Reductions - Budget (FY08), 2008. (Box 22)
  - Reductions - Targeted, 2015. (Box 20)
  - Reform proposals, 2010-2011. (Box 5)
  - Revenue Forecast, 2008-2010. (Box 4)
  - Session Conference issues, 2012. (Box 12)
  - Six Year Plan (2011-2016), 2011. (Box 6)
  - Veto Session budget concerns, 2007. (Box 28)
  - Vetoes - Governor Kaine, 2009. (Box 20)
  - Veto Session papers, 2011. (Box 3)
  - Veto Session issues, 2012. (Box 12)
  - Vetoes - Governor, 2013. (Box 15)
  - Walking around list, 2012. (Box 14)
  - Walking around list, 2013. (Box 13)
  - Year End Close, 2008-2010. (Box 2)
  - Year End Close - Fiscal, 2010. (Box 9)
  - Year End Close, 2011. (Box 18)
  - Year End Fiscal Budget Materials, 2012. (Box 14)